I I tell you ladies and gentlemen every
now and again I like to check in W with
our good friends on the Fox News Network
or or as your grandparents call it the
real news uh and and to be frank
oftentimes this show is critical of fox
but only because they're
terrible like sometimes almost
shockingly terrible for instance two
weeks ago justice department released a
report on the Ferguson Missouri Police
Department shooting of Michael Brown
basically exonerating officer Darren
Wilson and debunking the hands up don't
shoot narrative and then they released a
second doj report stating that the
Ferguson Police Department routinely
violates the Constitution and federal
law with a pattern of racial bias
unreasonable Force intentional
discrimination and mistreatment of
detainees wrongs born disproportionately
by
African-Americans but on Fox you're
going to love
this despite their 24-hour schedule they
really only had time for the one report
the doj now admitting hands up don't
shoot never happened people have been
fed a narrative protesters who have been
running around this country uh telling a
lie the tsunami of misinformation and
inuendo boneheaded non-f fact-based
rhetoric it never happened did not
happen it didn't happen that way
Wilson's been exonerated let's move on
let's move
on the Department of Justice found that
the flasho incident for protests did not
happen the way some thought although in
this second report they did also
document a tower of racially based
kindling wood years of unreasonable
Force lighter fluid and daily tossed lit
cigarette butts of discrimination and
harassment that could easily lend itself
to the
flasho but as the fire safety wardens of
fox
suggest let's just move
on
but here's the thing the anger is still
there the people couldn't move
on at
Fox they they they demanded restitution
at Fox why isn't the media which pedal
that narrative apologizing Obama
Sharpton they should be held responsible
for their incendiary rhetoric Banning
the Flames rushing to judgment blood on
their hands the damage was done or the
inflammatory rhetoric was used we saw
members of Congress saying hands up
don't shoot and if one of them has so
far apologized for misleading America we
haven't heard it I have not received a
single I am very
sorry for igniting racial conflict
greeting card hav seen
one the lesson Fox News is getting at is
very
clear wouldn't it be nice if people who
jump to conclusion and pedal a false
divisive anger stoking
narrative had to apologize for
misleading
America now
now here's where the gets
real I wonder if there is an analogous
event where we could test Fox's fty to
this principle of restitution for
agreement does the word Benghazi ring a
bell a bunch of new questions about
Benghazi Benghazi Benghazi Benghazi
Benghazi Benghazi Benghazi that first of
all Benghazi isn't Beetlejuice you don't
say it three
times but if you insist okay let's use
that example it's a tragic event where
Americans died like Ferguson but if the
analogy is to hold who will play the
role of nation dividing anger stoking
rhetoricians before the official
official government investigation was
completed Special Report investigates
death and deceit in Benghazi Susan Rice
willingly went along and lied on the
Sunday chat shows the CIA warned that
there might be an attack on the 9/11
anniversary during the attack they
didn't send help that was waiting in
Tripoli C130 to assist these guys coming
out they could have saved for Americans
but instead our government told them to
stand down
so basically you're saying the
government of the United States told its
military if I'm want to put this in a
catchy protesty kind of phrase stand
down don't
shoot and fox didn't restrict its anger
stoking to words because let's face it
their older viewers who are hard of
hearing also have a right to be mad so
scary opens and that burning Benghazi
footage in a semicontinuous loop like
some kind of Fox News U
log oh they're running the bir burning
compound footage again it seems like
benus comes earlier and earlier every
[Applause]
year but of course unlike Ferguson
protesters Fox wasn't being
irresponsible and divisive they just
wanted the truth we have unanswered
questions about Benghazi there are
glaring questions that are unanswered
questions still remain unanswered
there's questions about standown orders
and so on and here we are all the time
later we don't have the answers so we
still don't have the four Americans are
dead and there are a lot of uned
questions well your sentence
construction says I just want to know
but the tone says why the president had
an ambassador
whacked well finally on November 21st
2014 they got their answers from an
exhaustive report from the Republican
controlled house intelligence committee
answering those many questions did Susan
Rice go on TV and try to deceive anyone
report says no did the administration
ignore credible warnings about that
day's attack report says no was there a
standown order or failure to rescue
those
individuals and send rescued planes
report says no was there a massive
intelligence agency coverup report says
no not CIA not FBI none of them which
means all these elements in the two-year
Benghazi rage gasm
were what what do you call it what do
you call it uh tsunami of
misinformation bhe headed
non fact based rhetoric yes yes yes that
that right it's all those things so it
would only follow that just like Fox
demanded of any protester who said hands
up don't shoot the correct action for no
stand down don't shoot for Fox News now
would be too why isn't the media which
pedal that narrative apologizing yes yes
why not
yes oh Eric I'm that's so true yes
and so in the Fateful days following
that Republican house intelligence
committee
report what did the fox
[Music]
[Applause]
say in fact other than a couple of
half-hearted efforts to on the
Republican Le report its contents went
largely unnoticed on Fox Megan Kelly who
was prior to that desperately searching
for answers had the house intelligence
committee chair Mike Rogers onor show
two weeks after he released the Benghazi
report and never asked him about it once
not once yes the network who used the
word Benghazi like a clubhouse password
the official Republican dominated house
report on Benghazi was the only news
story in two years that didn't remind
them to talk about
Benghazi
which brings us once
again to our main point of respect and
appreciation the beauty that is the
ugliness of Fox
News they demand accountability for
anger and divisiveness whilst holding
themselves entirely unaccountable for
their anger and divisiveness for two
years they use Benghazi as shorthand as
a symbol for the whole concept of a
corrupt lying tyrannical possibly
murderous Obama White
House kind of like other people used
hands up don't shoot as a symbol for
systemic
racism and there's really only one
difference between the two
phenomenon systemic racism actually
[Applause]
exists